<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>2011 &#8211; Dispersion Translations</title>
	<atom:link href="/manga-release/2011/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:44:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>pt-BR</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Kagasarete Nairantou</title>
		<link>/manga/kagasarete-nairantou/</link>
					<comments>/manga/kagasarete-nairantou/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[link]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 18 Oct 2017 03:30:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.mangabooth.com/?post_type=wp-manga&#038;p=384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Ikuto Touhohin just had a last fight with his old man, one that led him to make a rash decision to run away from home. He boards a ship, deciding to take a vacation, but the ship is suddenly hit by a huge storm&#8211;one that sends Ikuto overboard! When he regains consciousness, he realizes he...<div class="c-read-more"><a class="c-read-more-link" href="/manga/kagasarete-nairantou/">Continue Reading</a> &#8594;</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Ikuto Touhohin just had a last fight with his old man, one that led him to make a rash decision to run away from home. He boards a ship, deciding to take a vacation, but the ship is suddenly hit by a huge storm&#8211;one that sends Ikuto overboard! When he regains consciousness, he realizes he is still alive… on some island. An isolated island. An isolated island with nothing but girls and talking animals. Stranded on an island with only girls, no electricity, gas, radio, television… like he was back in the stone age.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/manga/kagasarete-nairantou/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>6-ji kara 8-ji made</title>
		<link>/manga/6-ji-kara-8-ji-made/</link>
					<comments>/manga/6-ji-kara-8-ji-made/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[link]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 09:29:49 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.mangabooth.com/?post_type=wp-manga&#038;p=298</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Junko Sakuraban, a 27-year-old lecturer at an English conversation school has no boyfriend. Her parents set up a marriage interview for her with a man who turns out to be a Buddhist monk. However, Junko has no intention of becoming a temple wife, so she refuses to do the interview. Soon afterward, the man signs...<div class="c-read-more"><a class="c-read-more-link" href="/manga/6-ji-kara-8-ji-made/">Continue Reading</a> &#8594;</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Junko Sakuraban, a 27-year-old lecturer at an English conversation school has no boyfriend. Her parents set up a marriage interview for her with a man who turns out to be a Buddhist monk. However, Junko has no intention of becoming a temple wife, so she refuses to do the interview. Soon afterward, the man signs up to become her private student.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/manga/6-ji-kara-8-ji-made/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kyojin Shingeki no</title>
		<link>/manga/kyojin-shingeki-no/</link>
					<comments>/manga/kyojin-shingeki-no/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[link]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 09:16:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.mangabooth.com/?post_type=wp-manga&#038;p=290</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[In a world entirely ruled by giants, the human race, which has turned into their food, has surrounded its residential zones with immense walls, which both prevent their freedom outside the walls and protect them from incursions. However, as a result of the appearance of supergiants who cross the wall, a desperate struggle begins and...<div class="c-read-more"><a class="c-read-more-link" href="/manga/kyojin-shingeki-no/">Continue Reading</a> &#8594;</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>In a world entirely ruled by giants, the human race, which has turned into their food, has surrounded its residential zones with immense walls, which both prevent their freedom outside the walls and protect them from incursions. However, as a result of the appearance of supergiants who cross the wall, a desperate struggle begins and the young heroes, who have lost their parents, fight the giant as a training corps, with a view to regaining their freedom. Note: Won the Kodansha Manga Award in the shōnen category in 2011, was nominated for the 4th annual Manga Taishō award and also for the the 16th and 18th annual Tezuka Osamu Cultural Prize.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/manga/kyojin-shingeki-no/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>3</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Miharu Rokujou</title>
		<link>/manga/miharu-rokujou/</link>
					<comments>/manga/miharu-rokujou/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[link]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2017 04:14:19 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.mangabooth.com/?post_type=wp-manga&#038;p=243</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Apathetic schoolboy Miharu Rokujou is content to meander through life in the sleepy village of Banten. But his quiet existence is shattered when the Grey Wolves of Iga, a powerful ninja clan, attempt to kidnap him in broad daylight. Only then does Miharu discover that the ultimate power of the hidden ninja realm — a...<div class="c-read-more"><a class="c-read-more-link" href="/manga/miharu-rokujou/">Continue Reading</a> &#8594;</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Apathetic schoolboy Miharu Rokujou is content to meander through life in the sleepy village of Banten. But his quiet existence is shattered when the Grey Wolves of Iga, a powerful ninja clan, attempt to kidnap him in broad daylight. Only then does Miharu discover that the ultimate power of the hidden ninja realm — a power that can do both great good and great harm — is sealed within his body. As battles erupt among rival ninja clans seeking to control him, Miharu must overcome his apathy and learn the ways of the ninja if he wants any shot at survival!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/manga/miharu-rokujou/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>5</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
