<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Yuuta Tatsu &#8211; Dispersion Translations</title>
	<atom:link href="/manga-author/yuuta-tatsu/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2023 00:42:22 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>pt-BR</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.1.1</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Sai Tatsu</title>
		<link>/manga/sai-tatsu/</link>
					<comments>/manga/sai-tatsu/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[link]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 09:23:28 +0000</pubDate>
				<guid isPermaLink="false">http://demo.mangabooth.com/?post_type=wp-manga&#038;p=294</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A collection of short oneshots, all involving unrequited love in some form and that love sort of being returned with time. 1) 17 Sai Natsu Aki connfessed one year ago to Yoh, but he was going out with someone at the time. So, when she finds out they broke up; what she does might be...<div class="c-read-more"><a class="c-read-more-link" href="/manga/sai-tatsu/">Continue Reading</a> &#8594;</div>]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>A collection of short oneshots, all involving unrequited love in some form and that love sort of being returned with time. 1) 17 Sai Natsu Aki connfessed one year ago to Yoh, but he was going out with someone at the time. So, when she finds out they broke up; what she does might be good at first. But in the end will she be happy with Yoh? Or will something go horribly wrong? 2) 17 Sai Fuyu Yui loves Maki, her childhood friend, but does Maki love her? During winter break she goes to her aunt&#8217;s (where Maki lives) and confesses her love. Does Maki love her too? Or is she going to end up with a broken heart? 3) 17 Sai Haru One sentence is all I&#8217;ve ever wanted to hear from her. That&#8217;s all. I love her. But I can&#8217;t, I&#8217;m not allowed. She&#8217;s my brother&#8217;s fiance. Even so, I&#8217;ll do anything to make her mine. If I hurt her, bring her pain, well, as long as I can be with her. I don&#8217;t care if she hates me. 4) 17 Sai Aki Nao, in pain because of her unrequited love, confesses to and decides to go out with the brother of the one she loves. She believes this way, Yuuta could notice her at least. Maybe even more than a friend. Nao knows she isn&#8217;t a terribly attractive girl, but yet she wants to make Yuuta love her with any means possible.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/manga/sai-tatsu/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
